Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
Untertitel bereitgestellt von dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
♪Passing by where leaves fall and flowers fade♪
♪Vorbeigehen, wo Blätter fallen und Blumen verwelken♪
♪Chancing upon shooting stars and northern lights♪
♪Zufällig Sternschnuppen und Nordlichter sehen♪
♪At this moment, I borrow the wind♪
♪In diesem Moment leihe ich mir den Wind♪
♪To set sail for distant seas♪
♪In die fernen Meere aufbrechen♪
♪Rumors swirl close to my ears♪
♪Gerüchte wirbeln nah an meinen Ohren♪
♪Some laugh and say my dreams are wild♪
♪Manche lachen und sagen, meine Träume sind wild♪
♪Yet I will not change my original aspiration♪
♪Doch ich werde mein ursprüngliches Ziel nicht ändern♪
♪Even if it means running into a wall♪
♪Auch wenn es bedeutet, gegen eine Wand zu rennen♪
♪I know the road to growing up brings pain♪
♪Ich weiß, dass der Weg des Erwachsenwerdens schmerzhaft ist.♪
♪Still, I hold fast to the dream I cherish♪
♪Dennoch halte ich an dem Traum fest, den ich hege♪
♪Never have I thought to yield♪
♪Ich habe nie daran gedacht, nachzugeben♪
♪Youth is meant to stand against the world♪
♪Jugend ist dazu da , sich gegen die Welt zu behaupten♪
♪I've always longed♪
♪Ich habe mich immer danach gesehnt♪
♪To stand upon the highest peak♪
♪Auf dem höchsten Gipfel stehen♪
♪I've always wished♪
♪Ich habe mir immer gewünscht♪
♪To cross a river wide and deep♪
♪Einen breiten und tiefen Fluss überqueren♪
♪In darkness, look up to see the sky turn clear♪
♪ Schau in der Dunkelheit nach oben und sieh, wie der Himmel klar wird♪
♪Unyielding♪
♪Unnachgiebig♪
♪The butterfly reborn from its cocoon must fly♪
♪Der aus seinem Kokon wiedergeborene Schmetterling muss fliegen♪
♪Like bamboo breaking forth, I chase dreams through hardship♪
♪Wie ein Bambus, der ausbricht, verfolge ich Träume durch alle Schwierigkeiten ♪
♪Return to me, my dream♪
♪Kehre zu mir zurück, mein Traum♪
♪Unyielding♪
♪Unnachgiebig♪
♪My pure heart stays the same♪
♪Mein reines Herz bleibt dasselbe♪
♪You must face the wind♪
♪Du musst dem Wind trotzen♪
♪And go where your heart leads♪
♪Und geh, wohin dein Herz dich führt♪
♪Embrace the moonlight that belongs to you♪
♪Genieße das Mondlicht , das dir gehört♪
♪In the dark♪
♪Im Dunkeln♪
=Voyage to Haihun, Season 2=
=Reise nach Haihun, Staffel 2=
=Episode 14=
=Episode 14=
(Jingkou Village)
(Dorf Jingkou)
Why am I sleeping in bed?
Why am I sleeping in bed?
You sleepwalked.
You sleepwalked.
I sleepwalked?
I sleepwalked?
Yeah.
Ja.
Where did you sleep last night?
Where did you sleep last night?
Sorry about that.
Das tut mir leid.
Are you hungry?
Are you hungry?
No.
NEIN.
Want to eat something?
Want to eat something?
Heng.
Heng.
What are you doing?
Was machst du?
I'm changing clothes.
I'm changing clothes.
I'm a man, too.
I'm a man, too.
What do you want so early?
What do you want so early?
I came to check on you.
I came to check on you.
Don't come in.
Don't come in.
What's wrong? Let me in so we can talk.
What's wrong? Let me in so we can talk.
I'm not done changing.
I'm not done changing.
What? Is there a lady inside?
What? Is there a lady inside?
No.
NEIN.
Don't ruin my reputation.
Don't ruin my reputation.
Then open the door.
Then open the door.
I'm not done changing.
I'm not done changing.
How was it last night?
How was it last night?
Was it handled properly?
Was it handled properly?
Listen to me.
Listen to me.
The key is not to hurt the lady's heart.
The key is not to hurt the lady's heart.
Be honest
Be honest
with your feelings.
with your feelings.
Sincerity always matters most.
Sincerity always matters most.
- You... - Wait for me at the bridge.
- You... - Wait for me at the bridge.
I'll go find you after changing.
I'll go find you after changing.
Not going.
Not going.
I'm here to guide and teach you.
I'm here to guide and teach you.
I know your heart's long been with my senior.
I know your heart's long been with my senior.
Stop hiding your feelings.
Stop hiding your feelings.
It's been over ten years.
It's been over ten years.
Can you be a little braver?
Can you be a little braver?
Yes, my senior
Yes, my senior
may look rather stern,
may look rather stern,
but she's truly gentle inside.
but she's truly gentle inside.
The sacred herb is too potent.
The sacred herb is too potent.
It's making me hallucinate again.
It's making me hallucinate again.
Earth Rank family, come here.
Earth Rank family, come here.
Come here.
Komm her.
I must go call my senior.
I must go call my senior.
I'll take a look, too.
I'll take a look, too.
I'm coming as well.
I'm coming as well.
I'm coming, too.
I'm coming, too.
Family.
Familie.
Hear me out.
Hear me out.
Please set your mind at ease.
Please set your mind at ease.
These gold biscuits
These gold biscuits
will be delivered safely to your family.
will be delivered safely to your family.
We will tell them
We will tell them
you are doing well here.
you are doing well here.
- Great. - Good.
- Great. - Good.
Trust us. Every effort will be remembered.
Trust us. Every effort will be remembered.
Everyone will receive blessings.
Everyone will receive blessings.
Thanks to Mistress.
Danke an Herrin.
Always at Mistress's service.
Immer zu Diensten der Herrin.
Hey.
Hey.
What?
What?
Check that chest.
Check that chest.
- Me again? - Yes.
- Me again? - Yes.
Fine.
Fine.
Come on, family!
Come on, family!
- Keep up.
- Keep up.
It was my fault last night.
It was my fault last night.
De Jiu did the right thing.
De Jiu did the right thing.
Though I passed out,
Though I passed out,
I did wake up later.
I did wake up later.
I acted so willfully and recklessly.
I acted so willfully and recklessly.
I hope it didn't trouble you and De Jiu.
I hope it didn't trouble you and De Jiu.
I feel so guilty about it.
I feel so guilty about it.
No need, really.
No need, really.
This tea is quite good.
This tea is quite good.
- De Jiu. - Wait.
- De Jiu. - Wait.
Allow me.
Allow me.
Such fine tea.
Such fine tea.
You two have
You two have
important matters to discuss.
important matters to discuss.
I shouldn't stay.
I shouldn't stay.
I'll take my leave now.
I'll take my leave now.
There's nothing between me and her.
There's nothing between me and her.
She just came to offer an apology.
She just came to offer an apology.
An apology.
An apology.
Oh.
Oh.
I saw it.
I saw it.
Any leads?
Any leads?
They took the gold out for a stroll,
They took the gold out for a stroll,
found a hidden spot,
found a hidden spot,
and burned the cloth with the tags.
and burned the cloth with the tags.
Then, they brought it back.
Then, they brought it back.
Using the gold over and over.
Using the gold over and over.
No wonder they give it away so freely.
No wonder they give it away so freely.
Seems I must reveal the truth to all.
Seems I must reveal the truth to all.
The Marquis and I will help you.
The Marquis and I will help you.
Alright.
In Ordnung.
It's getting late.
Es wird spät.
You must be tired today.
You must be tired today.
Get some rest early.
Ruhen Sie sich früh aus.
Tonight, you must sleep on the bed.
Tonight, you must sleep on the bed.
I'll turn in first.
I'll turn in first.
Greetings, family.
Grüße, Familie.
Horse Wang, you've been deceived.
Horse Wang, you've been deceived.
The gold
The gold
never reached your family.
never reached your family.
They haul the gold out and then bring it back,
They haul the gold out and then bring it back,
using it over and over.
using it over and over.
All to trick you into working.
All to trick you into working.
Wang,
Wang,
you can't speak so recklessly.
you can't speak so recklessly.
I saw it with my own eyes.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Enough, Wang, stop talking.
Enough, Wang, stop talking.
Have you ever met Mistress?
Have you ever met Mistress?
Where would they get so much gold?
Where would they get so much gold?
Have you thought about that?
Have you thought about that?
Has your family truly received the gold?
Has your family truly received the gold?
Have you ever gotten a reply from them?
Have you ever gotten a reply from them?
Alright, enough.
Okay, genug.
As long as we work hard,
Solange wir hart arbeiten,
we'll earn the gold,
wir werden das Gold verdienen,
secure a place,
einen Platz sichern,
and receive Mistress's blessing.
und empfange den Segen der Herrin.
- Did you note it down? - Yeah.
- Hast du es dir notiert? - Ja.
Make sure to note it down.
Notieren Sie es unbedingt.
Why call yourself Horse Wang?
Warum nennen Sie sich Horse Wang?
You should be called Donkey Wang.
Sie sollten Esel Wang heißen.
A stubborn donkey.
Ein sturer Esel.
Greetings, family.
Grüße, Familie.
A good harvest today.
Eine gute Ernte heute.
Yeah.
Ja.
Greetings, family.
Grüße, Familie.
Family, greetings.
Familie, Grüße.
Greetings, Heaven Rank family.
Grüße, Heaven Rank-Familie.
Wish you joy today.
Wünsche dir heute Freude.
Sir.
Herr.
You've been deceived.
Sie wurden getäuscht.
Those gold biscuits
Diese goldenen Kekse
never reached your family.
hat Ihre Familie nie erreicht.
They carted the gold away and brought it back again
Sie haben das Gold weggebracht und wieder zurückgebracht
just to trick you into working here.
nur um Sie dazu zu bringen, hier zu arbeiten.
Impossible.
Unmöglich.
Greetings, family.
Grüße, Familie.
Greetings, Heaven Rank family.
Grüße, Heaven Rank-Familie.
May your day be filled with joy.
Möge Ihr Tag voller Freude sein.
Sir.
Herr.
We've been deceived.
Wir wurden getäuscht.
The gold
Das Gold
never reached our family.
hat unsere Familie nie erreicht.
What?
Was?
How dare you slander Mistress!
Wie können Sie es wagen, Herrin zu verleumden!
This man,
Dieser Mann,
though of Heaven Rank,
obwohl vom himmlischen Rang,
dares
wagt
to openly defame Mistress,
Herrin offen zu diffamieren,
claiming the gold meant for us never reached our family
behauptet, das für uns bestimmte Gold sei nie bei unserer Familie angekommen
and was taken back instead.
und wurde stattdessen zurückgenommen.
Utter nonsense.
Völliger Unsinn.
May you meet a grim end.
Möge dir ein düsteres Ende widerfahren.
- A grim end to you.
- Ein düsteres Ende für Sie.
Look.
Sehen.
They move the gold out
Sie schaffen das Gold heraus
and then destroy the bags and addresses.
und anschließend die Taschen und Adressen vernichten.
After that, they bring the gold back.
Danach bringen sie das Gold zurück.
This is just a trick to deceive you.
Dies ist nur ein Trick, um Sie zu täuschen.
Fake, all fake.
Falsch, alles falsch.
It must be fake.
Es muss eine Fälschung sein.
Fake.
Gefälscht.
You're lying.
Du lügst.
Family, listen to me.
Familie, hört mir zu.
This is a misunderstanding.
Das ist ein Missverständnis.
This here is Wang.
Das hier ist Wang.
He's new here.
Er ist neu hier.
He must've heard these rumors somewhere.
Er muss diese Gerüchte irgendwo gehört haben.
You shouldn't speak recklessly.
Man sollte nicht leichtsinnig sprechen.
Actually, Wang
Eigentlich, Wang
is a man with a kind heart.
ist ein Mann mit einem guten Herzen.
What he did was for our sake.
Was er getan hat, geschah zu unserem Wohl.
Right?
Rechts?
Family, don't get angry.
Familie, werdet nicht wütend.
Let's not spoil the harmony.
Lassen Sie uns die Harmonie nicht stören.
Alright, you may leave.
Gut, Sie können gehen.
Next time, don't say that.
Sag das nächste Mal nicht.
Don't say that next time.
Sag das nächstes Mal nicht.
Let's not spoil the harmony.
Lassen Sie uns die Harmonie nicht stören.
Sorry about that.
Das tut mir leid.
Making such a joke.
So einen Witz machen.
Unbelievable.
Unglaublich.
Wang.
Wang.
You mustn't talk nonsense like this again.
Du darfst nicht noch einmal solchen Unsinn reden.
You...
Du...
If we work diligently,
Wenn wir fleißig arbeiten,
we'll live better days.
wir werden bessere Tage erleben.
Mistress will bless us.
Die Herrin wird uns segnen.
They believe only what they want to believe.
Sie glauben nur, was sie glauben wollen.
Mental manipulation.
Mentale Manipulation.
Even more dreadful than Mishenfu.
Noch schrecklicher als Mishenfu.
What does that mean?
Was bedeutet das?
It must be an even stronger drug.
Es muss ein noch stärkeres Medikament sein.
It feeds on unrealistic wishes
Es nährt sich von unrealistischen Wünschen
to take hold of one's mind.
den Verstand einer Person in den Griff bekommen.
If that's the case...
Wenn das der Fall ist ...
Though wishes are but illusions,
Obwohl Wünsche nur Illusionen sind,
the sacred herb is real.
das heilige Kraut ist echt.
If we destroy the sacred herb,
Wenn wir das heilige Kraut zerstören,
wouldn't that shatter their foolish obsession?
würde das ihre törichte Besessenheit nicht zerstören?
If they fail their task,
Wenn sie ihre Aufgabe nicht erfüllen,
they'll be driven out of the village.
sie werden aus dem Dorf vertrieben.
Destroying the sacred herb will draw Mistress out.
Die Zerstörung des heiligen Krauts wird die Herrin hervorlocken.
It's easy to ruin the sacred herb.
Es ist leicht, das heilige Kraut zu ruinieren.
It fears water.
Es hat Angst vor Wasser.
Let's act in the middle of the night.
Lasst uns mitten in der Nacht handeln.
We must be careful.
Wir müssen vorsichtig sein.
If they see us,
Wenn sie uns sehen,
the villagers will go mad.
die Dorfbewohner werden verrückt.
Be careful.
Seien Sie vorsichtig.
The sacred herb is all gone?
Das heilige Kraut ist verschwunden?
The sacred herb is all gone!
Das heilige Kraut ist verschwunden!
All our efforts are wasted.
Alle unsere Bemühungen sind vergeblich.
Everything's for nothing now.
Jetzt ist alles umsonst.
Horse Wang.
Pferd Wang.
Why did you treat me this way?
Warum hast du mich so behandelt?
This...
Das...
I understand now.
Jetzt verstehe ich.
This is a trial.
Dies ist ein Prozess.
A trial of my will.
Eine Prüfung meines Willens.
I can't give in.
Ich kann nicht aufgeben.
I must hold on.
Ich muss durchhalten.
There's still time.
Es ist noch Zeit.
I'll head down to gather the sacred herb.
Ich werde hinuntergehen, um das heilige Kraut zu sammeln.
I can still make it before tomorrow's ceremony.
Ich kann es noch vor der morgigen Zeremonie schaffen .
Forty dan.
Vierzig und.
However hard you work tonight,
Wie hart du heute Abend auch arbeitest,
you still wouldn't finish it all.
Sie würden trotzdem nicht alles aufessen.
There's time; I'll make it in time.
Es ist noch Zeit, ich werde es rechtzeitig schaffen.
Why push yourself so hard?
Warum sich so anstrengen?
I'm not doing this just for myself.
Ich mache das nicht nur für mich selbst.
It's for my brother, Scalp Wang.
Es ist für meinen Bruder, Scalp Wang.
When he first came to Yuzhang,
Als er zum ersten Mal nach Yuzhang kam,
he refused Mistress's blessing
er verweigerte den Segen der Herrin
and left me.
und hat mich verlassen.
He turned to banditry.
Er wandte sich dem Banditentum zu.
He even dared to defy Mistress,
Er wagte es sogar, Herrin herauszufordern,
bringing harm to the land.
dem Land Schaden zufügen.
His sins are grave.
Seine Sünden sind schwerwiegend.
I'm working so hard now
Ich arbeite jetzt so hart
to atone for his wrongs.
um für sein Unrecht zu büßen.
If I can do that,
Wenn ich das kann,
both of us
wir beide
might find peace in the next life.
könnte im nächsten Leben Frieden finden.
So close.
So nah.
I'm so close.
Ich bin so nah dran.
Why treat me this way?
Warum behandelst du mich so?
I'm running out of time.
Mir läuft die Zeit davon.
This is my only chance
Das ist meine einzige Chance
to receive Mistress's blessing.
um den Segen der Herrin zu erhalten.
I'm so close
Ich bin so nah dran
to having a blissful afterlife.
auf ein glückseliges Leben nach dem Tod.
Mortals have no afterlife.
Sterbliche haben kein Leben nach dem Tod.
A mortal lives but one life.
Ein Sterblicher lebt nur ein Leben.
And that is the life you have now.
Und das ist das Leben, das Sie jetzt haben.
Horse Wang.
Pferd Wang.
Leave the village.
Verlasse das Dorf.
Go live your present life, will you?
Lebe dein jetziges Leben, ja?
What are you saying?
Was sagst du?
My present life?
Mein gegenwärtiges Leben?
Why do you think I yearn for a happy afterlife?
Warum, glauben Sie, sehne ich mich nach einem glücklichen Leben nach dem Tod?
Because this life has been full of hardship.
Denn dieses Leben war voller Härten.
I've suffered enough.
Ich habe genug gelitten.
You tell me to live in my present life,
Du sagst mir, ich soll in meinem gegenwärtigen Leben leben,
but what life do I have left?
aber welches Leben bleibt mir noch?
I've lost even the hope for an afterlife.
Ich habe sogar die Hoffnung auf ein Leben nach dem Tod verloren.
You two...
Ihr zwei...
You destroyed the sacred herb.
Du hast das heilige Kraut zerstört.
You carry heavy sins.
Du trägst schwere Sünden.
You're bound for the underworld.
Sie sind auf dem Weg in die Unterwelt.
Maybe...
Vielleicht...
If I kill you all,
Wenn ich euch alle töte,
will that redeem me?
wird mich das erlösen?
Horse Wang, snap out of it.
Pferd Wang, reiß dich zusammen.
Yes.
Ja.
I'll end you.
Ich werde dich erledigen.
Only by ending you can I atone.
Nur indem ich dich beende, kann ich Buße tun.
Then my next life will be blessed.
Dann wird mein nächstes Leben gesegnet sein.
Yes.
Ja.
I will end you all.
Ich werde euch alle vernichten.
I will end you.
Ich werde dich vernichten.
Seize them.
Ergreift sie.
They destroyed the sacred herb.
Sie zerstörten das heilige Kraut.
Hurry, seize them.
Beeil dich, schnapp sie dir.
Go.
Gehen.
After them.
Nach ihnen.
Quick, seize them.
Schnell, schnapp sie dir.
- Wang! - Stop.
- Wang! - Hör auf.
- Don't run! - Don't let them get away.
- Lauf nicht weg! - Lass sie nicht entkommen.
Don't run.
Lauf nicht weg.
- Seize them! - Stop!
- Ergreift sie! - Halt!
We can't go any further.
Wir können nicht weiter.
The Sacred Land is just ahead.
Das Heilige Land liegt direkt vor Ihnen.
If they go in, they'll face Heaven's wrath.
Wenn sie hineingehen, werden sie dem Zorn des Himmels ausgesetzt sein.
We must not enter.
Wir dürfen nicht eintreten.
Yes, they'll be punished by Heaven.
Ja, sie werden vom Himmel bestraft.
De Jiu!
De Jiu!
Is this the Sacred Land's mysterious power?
Ist dies die geheimnisvolle Macht des Heiligen Landes ?
Careful.
Vorsichtig.
Wang.
Wang.
Are they specters?
Sind sie Gespenster?
Don't be afraid.
Hab keine Angst.
It's just miasma all around.
Es ist einfach überall Miasma.
Or maybe just a trick of the light.
Oder vielleicht nur ein Lichttrick.
Let's find De Jiu.
Lasst uns De Jiu finden.
De Jiu.
De Jiu.
Isn't this where the ghosts just passed?
Sind hier nicht gerade die Geister vorbeigezogen?
That way.
Auf diese Weise.
Strange.
Seltsam.
We can't get out of this fog.
Wir kommen aus diesem Nebel nicht heraus.
Why don't we wait till dawn?
Warum warten wir nicht bis zum Morgengrauen?
The mist will clear then.
Dann lichtet sich der Nebel.
I'm worried they might be in danger.
Ich mache mir Sorgen, dass sie in Gefahr sein könnten.
Wang.
Wang.
If we keep going in circles, we'll just wear ourselves out.
Wenn wir uns immer im Kreis drehen, erschöpfen wir uns nur.
Don't worry.
Mach dir keine Sorge.
Qi and De Jiu will be fine.
Qi und De Jiu wird es gut gehen.
Those villagers have lost their senses.
Diese Dorfbewohner haben den Verstand verloren.
No one knows what they might do.
Niemand weiß, was sie tun könnten.
Why must you oppose Mistress?
Warum müssen Sie sich der Herrin widersetzen?
From what I see, the villagers are all willing.
Soweit ich sehe, sind alle Dorfbewohner dazu bereit.
Since they choose to stay,
Da sie sich entscheiden zu bleiben,
it means they feel content here.
es bedeutet, dass sie sich hier wohl fühlen.
They've been deceived by false promises.
Sie wurden durch falsche Versprechungen getäuscht.
Mortals can only live in the present moment.
Sterbliche können nur im gegenwärtigen Augenblick leben .
There's no such thing as the next life.
So etwas wie das nächste Leben gibt es nicht.
But in times like these,
Aber in Zeiten wie diesen,
where can they find contentment?
wo können sie Zufriedenheit finden?
I don't know where,
Ich weiß nicht wo,
but I know happiness can't be built on lies.
aber ich weiß, dass Glück nicht auf Lügen aufgebaut werden kann.
I believe it's right here with Mistress.
Ich glaube, es ist genau hier bei Herrin.
Lan'er, Mistress is not what she seems.
Lan'er, Herrin ist nicht das, was sie zu sein scheint.
Your parents are the real ones.
Deine Eltern sind die wahren.
Don't give up.
Gib nicht auf.
You will find your parents for sure.
Du wirst deine Eltern bestimmt finden.
Until that day comes,
Bis dieser Tag kommt,
stay with us.
bleiben Sie bei uns.
We will look after you.
Wir kümmern uns um Sie.
Thank you, Wang...
Danke, Wang ...
Lan'er.
Lan'er.
♪Watch the storm; hear the night rain fall♪
♪Beobachte den Sturm, höre den nächtlichen Regen fallen♪
♪Till the light of dawn♪
♪Bis zum Morgengrauen♪
♪A truth that cannot be spoken♪
♪Eine Wahrheit, die nicht ausgesprochen werden kann♪
♪Right and wrong matter♪
♪Richtig und Falsch sind wichtig♪
♪Yet I can't make the right choice♪
♪Dennoch kann ich nicht die richtige Wahl treffen♪
♪The lost player in the game♪
♪Der verlorene Spieler im Spiel♪
♪Made a move by a twist of fate♪
♪ Durch eine Laune des Schicksals einen Schritt gemacht ♪
♪The way back is lost, leaving nowhere to return♪
♪Der Weg zurück ist verloren, es gibt keinen Ort, an den man zurückkehren kann♪
♪Borrow the endless cycles♪
♪Leih dir die endlosen Zyklen aus♪
♪To fight for the most perfect outcome♪
♪Für das perfekteste Ergebnis kämpfen♪
♪How to trace the threads and follow cause and effect♪
♪Wie man den Fäden folgt und Ursache und Wirkung erkennt♪
♪Seeking a strategy without flaw♪
♪ Auf der Suche nach einer Strategie ohne Fehler ♪
♪How to break free from this fated yet unforeseen lock♪
♪Wie man sich aus diesem schicksalhaften, aber unvorhergesehenen Schloss befreit ♪
♪To live so as to shake the world♪
♪ So leben, dass die Welt erschüttert wird♪
♪With this journey, I gain a fiercer edge♪
♪Mit dieser Reise gewinne ich an Schärfe♪
♪I've planned before I act countless times♪
♪Ich habe unzählige Male geplant, bevor ich gehandelt habe.♪
♪Fatal danger turned into a jest♪
♪ Aus tödlicher Gefahr wird ein Scherz♪
♪Through this road, I watch the endless rise and fall♪
♪Auf dieser Straße beobachte ich das endlose Auf und Ab♪
♪In the chapters lie ages of decay and bloom♪
♪In den Kapiteln liegen Zeitalter des Verfalls und der Blüte♪
♪Let us meet again♪
♪Lasst uns wiedersehen♪
♪One hurried path, and one at ease♪
♪Ein eiliger Weg und einer der Ruhe♪